export default [
  {
    // LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1 LEVEL 1
    video: require("../assets/videos/kendrickGQ.mp4"),
    question: "Which artist is Kendrick Lamar talking about?",
    options: ["2Pac", "Eminem", "Andre 3000"],
    correct_option: "Eminem",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/afterHours.webp"),
    question: "When did The Weeknd release his album After Hours?",
    options: ["20th March 2020", "20th September 2020"],
    correct_option: "20th March 2020",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/justDontGive.mp3"),
    question: "Which artist does this song belong to?",
    options: ["Yelawolf", "Jedi Mind Tricks", "Slim Shady"],
    correct_option: "Slim Shady",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/watchTheThrone.webp"),
    question: "Which producer did Kanye reach out for a few key assists?",
    options: ["Metro Boomin", "Q-Tip", "London on da Track"],
    correct_option: "Q-Tip",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/kidsSeeGhost.webp"),
    question: "Which artist doesn't have a feature on this album?",
    options: ["Mos Def", "Ty Dolla Sign", "2 Chainz"],
    correct_option: "2 Chainz",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/macMillerRain.mp3"),
    question: "What album is this song from?",
    options: [
      "Mac Miller - Faces",
      "Vince Staples - Prima Donna",
      "The Game - The Documentary",
    ],
    correct_option: "Mac Miller - Faces",
  },
  {
    video: require("../assets/videos/jcoleBeat.mp4"),
    question: "Which artist got the opportunity to rap on this beat?",
    options: ["Wale", "6LACK", "Caleborate"],
    correct_option: "Caleborate",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/compton.webp"),
    question: "Which month and year did Dr. Dre release his album Compton?",
    options: [" June 2016", "August 2015", " May 2014"],
    correct_option: "August 2015",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/mgkBreaking.mp3"),
    question: "Who is this artist?",
    options: ["Jack Harlow", "Logic", "Machine Gun Kelly"],
    correct_option: "Machine Gun Kelly",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/travisScott.webp"),
    question: "What is Travis Scott's real name?",
    options: [
      "Jacques Bermon Webster II",
      "Jacques Mescudi II",
      "Bermon Jacques Webster",
    ],
    correct_option: "Jacques Bermon Webster II",
  },
  {
    // LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2 LEVEL 2
    video: require("../assets/videos/logic44.mp4"),
    question: "What song is Logic recording?",
    options: ["44 Bars", "44 More", "Perfect"],
    correct_option: "44 More",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/cudiKanye.webp"),
    question: "Where did Kid Cudi meet Kanye west for the first time?",
    options: ["Sunset Sound Recorders", "BAPE Store", "Venice Beach"],
    correct_option: "BAPE Store",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/viceCity.mp3"),
    question: "XXXTentacion sampled who for his song - Vice City?",
    options: ["Laura Mvula", "Canis Major", "Imany"],
    correct_option: "Laura Mvula",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/d12.webp"),
    question: "How many songs does this album contain?",
    options: ["19", "21", "23"],
    correct_option: "21",
  },
  {
    video: require("../assets/videos/jayZ.mp4"),
    question: "What album is Jay-Z recording here?",
    options: ["The Blueprint", "American Gangster", "The Black Album"],
    correct_option: "The Black Album",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/50cent.webp"),
    question: "How many times has 50 Cent been shot?",
    options: ["5 times", "2 times", "9 times"],
    correct_option: "9 times",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/wuTangClan.mp3"),
    question: "Which group does this song belong to?",
    options: ["Cypress Hill", "Wu-Tang Clan", "The Roots"],
    correct_option: "Wu-Tang Clan",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/dmx.webp"),
    question: "How old was dmx when he started his career?",
    options: ["14 years old", "21 years old", "17 years old"],
    correct_option: "14 years old",
  },
  {
    song: require("../assets/music/geazyBadBoy.mp3"),
    question: "Who is G-Eazy dissing in this song?",
    options: ["Lil Wayne", "Machine Gun Kelly", "Asap Rocky"],
    correct_option: "Machine Gun Kelly",
  },
  {
    pic: require("../assets/images/macklemore.webp"),
    question: "How many views has Macklemore's song 'Thrift Shop' on youtube?",
    options: ["1.6 Billion views", "800 Million views", "1.1 Billion views"],
    correct_option: "1.6 Billion views",
  },
  // {  //LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3 LEVEL 3
  //     video: require('../assets/videos/joynerLucas.mp4'),
  //     question: "Which artist made this grammy nominated video?",
  //     options: ["Joyner Lucas","Chance The Rapper","J Cole"],
  //     correct_option: "Joyner Lucas"
  // },
  // {
  //     pic: require('../assets/images/popSmoke.webp'),
  //     question: "Which song made Pop Smoke famous?",
  //     options: ["PTSD","Meet the Woo", "Dior"],
  //     correct_option: "Dior",
  // },
  // {
  //     song: require('../assets/music/viceCity.mp3'),
  //     question: "Which song made Pop Smoke famous?",
  //     options: ["PTSD", "Meet the Woo", "Dior"],
  //     correct_option: "Dior"
  // },
  // {
  //     pic: require('../assets/images/d12.webp'),
  //     question: "How many songs does this album contain?",
  //     options: ["19","21","23"],
  //     correct_option: "21",
  // },
  // {
  //     video: require('../assets/videos/jayZ.mp4'),
  //     question: "What album is Jay-Z recording here?",
  //     options: ["The Blueprint","American Gangster", "The Black Album"],
  //     correct_option: "The Black Album"
  // },
  // {
  //     pic: require('../assets/images/50cent.webp'),
  //     question: "How many times has 50 Cent been shot?",
  //     options: ["5 times","2 times", "9 times"],
  //     correct_option: "9 times",
  // },
  // {
  //     song: require('../assets/music/wuTangClan.mp3'),
  //     question: "Which group does this song belong to?",
  //     options: ["Cypress Hill", "Wu-Tang Clan", "The Roots"],
  //     correct_option: "Wu-Tang Clan"
  // },
  // {
  //     pic: require('../assets/images/dmx.webp'),
  //     question: "How old was dmx when he started his career?",
  //     options: ["14 years old","21 years old","17 years old"],
  //     correct_option: "14 years old"
  // },
  // {
  //     song: require('../assets/music/geazyBadBoy.mp3'),
  //     question: "Who is G-Eazy dissing in this song?",
  //     options: ["Lil Wayne", "Machine Gun Kelly", "Asap Rocky"],
  //     correct_option: "Machine Gun Kelly"
  // },
  // {
  //     pic: require('../assets/images/macklemore.webp'),
  //     question: "How many views has Macklemore's song 'Thrift Shop' on youtube?",
  //     options: ["1.6 Billion views","800 Million views", "1.1 Billion views"],
  //     correct_option: "1.6 Billion views",
  // },
];
